Guide to the Kenneth J. Arrow Papers, 1939-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Miscellaneous Series, 1950-1993 (bulk 1970s-1993).
  Comprised of the Prizes, Awards, and Honors Subseries, which includes correspondence surrounding his Nobel Prize award of 1970; the Personal (Arrow) Files Subseries, which includes biographical material and interviews, real estate activities, security clearance, and other private files; the Business and Publishers Subseries, which includes reprint permissions and correspondence with publishers; and the Referee Reports, and Book, Grant, and Other Reviews Subseries, which includes reviews of papers, books, and grants.
  - Prizes, Awards, and Honors Subseries (Box 36)
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences fellow award, 1959 (Box 53)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science fellow award, 1980 (Box 53)
    - American Economic Association, distinguished fellow award, ND (Box 53)
    - American Philosophical Society fello award, 1968 (Box 53)
    - American Statistical Association, fellow award, 1959 (Box 53)
    - APSA-Lippincott, 2009 (Box 51)
    - Cambridge Honorary Degree, 1985 (Box 36)
    - Catholic University of the Sacred Heart, 1994 (Box 53)
    - City College of New York bachelor's degree, 1940 (Box 53)
    - Columbia University MA Degree, 1941 (Box 53)
    - Columbia University Doctor of Philosophy degree, 1951 (Box 53)
    - Columbia University honorary degree, 1973 (Box 53)
    - Cyprus University honorary degree, ND (Box 53)
    - Finnish Academy of Science honorary degree, 1975 (Box 53)
    - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1974-92 (Box 36)
    - Graduate Faculties Alumni of Columbia University (GFA) award, 1982 (Box 36)
    - Harvard University honorary degree (related documents), 1999 (Box 51)
    - Harvard University honorary degree, 1999 (Box 53)
    - Harvard University honorary MA degree, 1967 (Box 53)
    - Hebrew University of Jerusalem honorary degree and photo album, 1975 (Box 53)
    - International Award of the Indian Econometric Society, 1975 (Box 36)
    - Institute of Medicine of the National Academy of Sciences membership certficate, 1974 (Box 53)
    - Certificate in Japanese (Box 53)
    - Jewish Hall of Fame, 1989 (Box 36)
    - John Bates Clark Award (AEA) medal, 1957 (Box 53)
    - John H. Finley award, 1975 (Box 53)
    - National Academy of Sciences fellow award, 1968 (Box 53)
    - National Medal of Science, 2005 (Box 51)
    - Neumann Theory Prize, 1986 (Box 36)
    - Neumann Theory Prize award and medal, 1986 (Box 53)
    - New York University, United States Air Forces meteorological training certificate, 1943 (Box 53)
    - New York University honorary degree, 1972 (Box 53)
    - Nobel Prize (Box 36)
      - Royal Academy of Sciences (Box 36)
      - speech, 1972 (Box 36)
      - ceremonies, 1972 (Box 36)
      - references to work and publications, 1972-73 (Box 36)
      - Kuratorom and Nominations, 1982-92 (Box 36)
      - nominations, 1972-78 (Box 36)
      - nomination for Amartya Sen, 1986 (Box 36)
      - nomination for W. Edwards Deming, 1991 (Box 36)
      - Jubilee, 1991 (Box 36)
      - contract symposium, 1988-90 (Box 36)
    - American Nobel Anniversary Committee, 1990 (Box 36)
    - Pontifical Academy of Social Sciences honorary degree, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Rene Descartes University honorary degree, 1974 (Box 53)
    - Sacro Cuore Degree, 1994 (Box 51)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon, 1986 (Box 36)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon, certificate, 1986 (Box 53)
    - Sigma Xi, 1982 (Box 36)
    - Tel Aviv University honorary degree, 1998 (Box 53)
    - Townsend Harris Medal, 1973 (Box 53)
    - Townsend Harris High School certificate of college eligibility, 1936 (Box 53)
    - United States Army Meteorological Officers certificate, 1943 (Box 53)
    - University fo Buenos Aires honorary degree, 1999 (Box 53)
    - University of Chicago, Doctor of Laws degree, 1967 (Box 53)
    - University of Law, Economics, and Science of Aix-Marseilles honorary degree, 1985 (Box 53)
    - University of Pennsylvania honorary degree, 1976 (Box 53)
    - University of the State of New York (SUNY), college entrance diploma, 1936 (Box 53)
    - University of Vienna honorary degree, 1971 (Box 53)
    - Uppsala Degree (related documents), 1994 (Box 51)
    - Uppsala Degree, 1994 (Box 53)
    - Washington University honorary degree, 1989 (Box 36)
    - Washington University honorary degree (2), 1989 (Box 53)
    - Yale University honorary degree, 1974 (Box 53)
  - Personal (Arrow) Files Subseries
    - Academe Article (Interview), 2006 (Box 51)
    - Biographical material, 1968-72 (Box 36)
    - Biographical sketch (includes photographs), 1975 (Box 36)
    - Birthday-65th, 1986 (Box 51)
    - Birthday-70th, 1991 (Box 51)
    - Columbia 70th Birthday Seminar, 1991 (Box 51)
    - Birthday-80th, 2001 (Box 51)
    - Early Career (Box 51)
    - German Television (interview), 1988-89 (Box 36)
    - Long Ridge (real estate), 1978 (Box 36)
    - Personal-miscellaneous, 1968-72 (Box 36)
    - Personal security information, 1950 (Box 36)
    - Stanford Hospital, 2004 (Box 51)
    - Townsend Harris Alumni Association, 1980-91 (Box 36)
    - Who's Who in World Jewry, 1976-77 (Box 36)
  - Business and Publishers Subseries
    - Abt Books, 1982-88 (Box 36)
    - Arthur D. Little, 1973 (Box 36)
    - Basil Blackwell, 1982-83 (Box 36)
    - Book Permissions, 1987-88 (Box 36)
    - Cambridge University Press, 1990-96 (Box 51)
    - Debreu Archives, 2002 (Box 51)
    - Elsevier, 1973-74 (Box 36)
    - Granger Translation, 2000 (Box 51)
    - Harcourt Preface, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Harvard Book-author permissions, 1982-84 (Box 36)
    - Holden Day, 1969-79 (Box 36)
    - Holden Day, 1969-1979 (continued) (Box 37)
    - Hotelling Bio, 2005 (Box 51)
    - Irwin, 1982-89 (Box 37)
    - Italian Translation, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1978-89 (Box 37)
    - Karlin Memorial Resolution, 2007 (Box 51)
    - H. Kurz-Letter on Growth (Box 51)
    - Limits of Organization, 1983-88 (Box 37)
    - Mansfield Bio, 1999 (Box 51)
    - Markham, 1963-70 (Box 37)
    - Nasar Book, 2003 (Box 51)
    - North-Holland, 1975-88 (Box 51)
    - Norton, 1973-74 (Box 51)
    - Oxford University Press, 1990-93 (Box 51)
    - Patent agreement and misc. contracts, 1979 (Box 51)
    - Payroll Information, 1979 (Box 51)
    - Permissions, 1979-94 (Box 37)
    - Permissions Granted, 1994-99 (Box 51)
    - Popular papers, 1984 (Box 37)
    - Princeton University Press, 1994 (Box 37)
    - Resources for the Future, 1979-84 (Box 37)
    - Routledge, 1989-92 (Box 37)
    - Scarf Tribute, 1992 (Box 51)
    - Simon Memorial, 2003 (Box 51)
    - Social Choice Chinese Translation, 1999 (Box 51)
    - Szenberg Forward, 2006 (Box 51)
    - TLC Media, 1999 (Box 51)
    - Tversky Memorial, 1997 (Box 51)
    - Zygmunt Gebethner, 1975 (Box 37)
  - Referee Reports, and Book, Grant, and Other Reviews Subseries
    - Referee reports, 1978-93, (3 folders) (Box 37)
    - Referee Reports, 1994-03, (3 folders) (Box 52)
    - Referee Requests (Box 52)
    - Economic and Social Research Council (ESRC)-Referee Reports (Box 52)
    - NAS-Referee Reports (Box 52)
    - Miscellaneous evaluations and reviews, 1980-85 (Box 37)
    - Aizerman, M.A., and F.T. Aleskerov, Choice of Variants, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Brenner, Harvey, The Effects of Health Care and Health Promotion on Health Status in the United States, 1989 (Box 37)
    - Cooper Comment, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Dummet Review, 1997 (Box 52)
    - Ehrlich Comment, 2002 (Box 52)
    - Guttman Comment, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Hahn, Frank, Risk, Information, and Quality Signals in Economic Theory, 1993 (Box 37)
    - Lieberman Paper, 1998 (Box 52)
    - Myerson, Roger, Game Theory, 1991 (Box 37)
    - Nozick, Robert, 1974 (Box 37)
    - Olson Review, 2000 (Box 52)
    - Partisan Review (correspondence), 1982 (Box 37)
    - Radin Review, 1997 (Box 52)
    - Thurow, Lester, Dangerous Currents, 1983 (Box 37)